"其它人"就要来了
The Others are coming.
我们只有3个选择  跑  躲  要么就是死
You have only three choices: Run, hide, or die.
我们确实有个计划
We do have a plan.
你去丛林里弄些炸药回来
Yeah, go to the jungle,
然后炸开舱盖让大家躲进去
get some dynamite, blow open a hatch,hide everyone inside.
不
No.
停下  快停下
Stop! Stop it!
停下  我们不能这么做
Stop it, we can't!
停下  别点着
Stop, don't light it!
声明: 本字幕由YYeTs美剧字幕组原创翻译制作
欢迎访问官方论坛  www.YYeTs.net 在线观看 剧情讨论 学习交流
=====本字幕由以下成员荣誉制作 感谢他们的无私奉献======
翻译：skier_airman校对：扣扣
后期：xyz 双语制作：冰小赐  雯雯  七色九天
========== 字幕总监制：七色九天 ==========
迷 失
第二季 第一集
4  8  我们死定了  15  注定要死了...
4, 8, We're dead. 15. Doomed and dead.
Hurley  你还好吧?
Hurley, you OK?
噢  是的  还不错  我想去尿尿
Huh? Yeah. Awesome.I just...have to pee.
好主意  你们两个...去看看那个着火的死亡之洞吧
Great idea, dude, go look in the burning death hole.
这到底是什么?
What is it?
是什么并不重要
It doesn't matter what it is.
我们炸开舱门就能让大家在里面安全避难了么?
We blew the door so we could get everyone inside so they'd be safe.
这计划不会管用的
That plan is not gonna work.
我们不可能让大家都能及时下去
We'll never get everyone down in time.
-是水  -很浅  更像是一个污水坑
-Water.  -Shallow. Sounds like a puddle.
-大概...在下面40英尺处?  -最多50
-40 feet down?  -50, tops.
我们可以用从机身上拉下来的绳子
We could use the wire from the fuselage,
绕在身上作为保护
rig up a harness...
-John  我们要走了  -是的  好主意  我们照做好了
-John, we're leaving now.  -Yes. Great idea, let's do that.
我们经历了好多磨难才走到这一步  Jack
We all went through a lot to get here.
梯子已经坏了
The ladder is broken.
你要让40个人一个个从这儿下去?
You're gonna lower 40 people down there one by one?
他们正等着我们回去告诉他们怎么做
They're waiting for us to tell them what do,
别去做那什么保护索了
so forget the harnesses.
Jack
怎么?
What?
我们还是冷静一下吧
Why don't we all just calm down here?
听着  如果你想在白天下去探险的话  没问题
No, if you wanna go exploring in the morning, fine,
但是今晚  我们收工了
but tonight we're done.
我去拿我们没用过的炸药  然后我们回营地去
I'm gonna get the dynamite we didn't use and we're heading back to the caves.
John  你来帮忙包炸药怎么样?
So how about you pack it up, John?
可以  当然可以
Sure. Of course.
好的
OK.
Jack  你为什么不想下去看看?
Why don't you want to go down there,Jack?
女性  将近30岁  没有身份证明
Female, late twenties, no ID.
她第二次来这儿做电击了
Coded twice on the way over here...
另一个呢?
Where's the other one?
在我们后面  马上来了
They're on their way.
消防队得占用一下进口
Fire department had to use the jaws.
伤者的情况?
What do we got?
女性  将近30岁
Female, late twenties, auto accident.
那到底是什么东西?
What is that?
驾驶杆的一部分
A piece of the steering column.
好了  我们开始  抓稳她的领口
Let's go. Keep that collar steady.
-让我爸记录了么?  -已经说了
-Page my father  -Already did.
-详细情况  -她的车爆胎了
-Tell me.  -Her tire blew.
车子飞过了隔离带  撞上了一辆城市越野车
car jumped the divider,hit an SUV.
血压一直在下降
BP's dropping!
-车是她开得么?  -是的  就她一个人
-Pericardial's pierced. Was she driving?  -Yeah. Alone.
城市越野车的驾驶员呢?
Where's the driver of the SUV?
Adam Rutherford  57岁  胸口外伤  没有呼吸了
Adam Rutherford, 57,chest trauma, no breath sounds.
-给Rutherford插管...  -我不会插管  应该你来
-Tube Mr Rutherford...  -I can't intubate, you've got to.
Sheppard医生  她的血压已经降到60到80了
Dr Shephard, her BP's 80/60.
好了  我要一个注射器  大点的
OK. I need a syringe. A big one.
你  帮忙压紧点
You, hold pressure.
52到88了  没有脉搏了
88 over 52, no radial pulse.
我知道  知道  都是血
I know, I know. Sac's flooded.
-注射器  -给你
-Where's that...  -Here.
-可以了么?  -是的
-Got it?  -Yep.
血压稳定了
BP's stabilizing.
死亡时间  早上8点15分
Time of death: 8.15am.
好了  我要血液气体
OK. Get me a blood gas and a C spine.
把她带去重症监护室  别让她动
Get her up to ICU and keep her immobilised.
我想在婚礼上...跳舞
I wanna dance at my wedding.
你听到了么?
Did you hear that?
亲爱的  你得放松一下  好么?  放轻松点
You need to take it easy, OK?Just relax...
她说什么?
What did she say?
她说她想在她婚礼上跳舞
She said she has to dance at her wedding.
那儿没人
OK, no one is out there.
没人会来的
No one is coming.
但是那个法国女人说过...
But the French woman said...
那个法国女人有点不正常  你知道么?
The French woman is missing a bloody wing nut.
我是说  那全是胡说的  只是一个鬼故事罢了
I mean, it was all bollocks.It's a ghost story.
黑烟是她自己点的
She set the fire herself.
怎么了?
What?
没什么
Nothing.
有人见到Vincent么?
Has anyone seen Vincent?
那只狗  有人见到它么?
The dog? Anyone seen him?
有人看见那只狗么?
Has anyone seen the dog?
你去哪儿?
Where are you going?
那只狗走丢了
I lost the damn dog.
你为什么这么做?
Why'd you do that?
你为什么要点燃导火线?
Why'd you light the fuse, man?
我为什么不点呢?
Why wouldn't I light the fuse?
因为我正跑向你
Maybe because I was running towards you,
挥着手  大叫着  别这么做
waving my arms,yelling, "Don't do that!"
恩  你说到点子上了
Well, you've got a point there.
我猜可能是因为我很想进去看看吧
I guess I was excited to get inside.
我是说我们就是为了这个而来的  不是么?
That's why we came here, isn't it?
就是为了这个我们才这么大老远跑去"黑岩石"那儿
That's why we went out to the Black Rock,
带回炸药炸开了舱盖
and got the dynamite to blow the hatch.
我们这么做了所以我们才能躲进去  Hugo
We did it so we could get inside, Hugo.
然后拯救大家
And to save everybody's lives.
And to save everyone's lives.
或者说这就是我们的命运  对么  John?
Or maybe it was just our destiny. Right, John?
也许是
Maybe.
伙计们  呃  这个舱盖...
Guys. It's the hatch door.
你们最好过来看看
You'd better see this.
检疫隔离
Vincent
别走太远了
This is not a good idea.
5分钟前我还看见它的
I saw him five minutes ago.
况且你也说过  那儿根本没有其它人
Besides,you said there wasn't anyone out here.
我是说我们没见到任何人
I said we didn't see anyone.
那只狗会自己回来的  它总是这样的
The dog will come back on his own,he always does.
看管那只狗是别人第一次拜托我的事
Watching that dog was the one thing anybody ever asked me to do.
如果它有个什么三长两短...
If something happens to him...
你上一次睡觉或是吃东西是在什么时候?
When was the last time you slept or had something to eat?
你已经有点虚脱了
You're exhausted.
我不能告诉那个孩子我丢了他的狗只是因为我太累了
I can't tell that kid I lost his dog because I was exhausted.
我从后面抓它
I'll circle around behind him.
好的
OK.
Vincent
Sayid
你在哪儿?  Sayid
Where are you!? Sayid!
Sayid
Walt?
你在这儿干什么?
What are you doing here?
Shannon
怎么了?
What is it?
什么?
What?
你为什么这么想下去?
Why do you want to get down there so bad?
小姐  我为什么这么想下去?
"- Ly". Why do I want to get down there so "badly"?
Jack认为我疯了  是么?
Jack thinks I'm crazy, doesn't he?
为什么?  因为你想从一个写着"检疫隔离"
Why? Cos you want to drop into a hatch that's been locked from the inside
并从里面锁住了的舱门里进去?
by a foot-thick steel door that says "Quarantine"?
恩  往好的方面想想吧  舱门已经被毁了
Look at the bright side:The damage is done.
好的方面
Bright side.
如果Jack认为我有点疯狂  我不怪他  真的
And if Jack thinks I've lost it,I can't blame him, really.
并且5个小时以前  我差点被一个看起来
Then again, five hours ago I was pulled into a hole
像柱状的黑烟拉进洞里
by what appeared to be a column of black smoke.
你看到了么  Kate?
Did you see it, Kate?
那么我想我们都疯了
Then I guess we're both crazy.
想想Jack认为他看见了什么
I wonder what Jack thinks he saw.
伙计  你得有所行动了
You should go ahead, man.
别让Locke有时间和你的女人在一起
Don't want Locke making time with your girl.
伙计  说笑罢了
Joke, dude.
现在没有这个心情  Hurley
Not really in the mood, Hurley.
真的么?  你通常总像是哈哈先生
Really? Wow.Usually you're like, Mr Ha-ha.
你想想
There ya go.
生活不是那么糟糕  是么?
Life's not so bad, right?
我是说  是的  "其它人"就要来...也许是吃了我们
Sure, the Others are coming to like, eat us all,
然后偶尔的  有些人把火气全撒在你头上
and every once in a while someone blows up all over you,
但是我们每天还是要睡觉的
but we do get to sleep in every morning.
恩哈  那些数字怎么说?
And the numbers?
什么?
What?
"那些不是好数字"
"The numbers are bad. "
当我扭住你的时候你是这么叫的
That's what you were yelling right when I tackled you.
-是的  说来话长  -我有时间
-Yeah. It's kind of a long story.  -I've got time.
-你会认为我疯了  -说说看
-You'll think I'm crazy.  -Try me.
以前  我在神经病监护室的时候
A while ago, I was in this kind of psych ward
有个叫Leonard的人
and there was this guy, Leonard.
我每次见到他  他总是在说这些数字
All the time I knew him,all he ever said were these numbers.
4,8,15,16,23,42,一遍一遍又一遍的重复
"4, 8, 15, 16, 23, 42".Over and over and over again.
然后它们就深深得印在我的脑子里了
And they kind of got stuck in my head.
当我出来的时候
So when I got out...
呃  实际上是当我出来后几个月
well, actually a couple months after I got out,
有次我在买冰冻墨西哥玉米煎饼的时候 我突然想我该去玩彩票
I was buying a frozen burrito and thought "I should play the lottery",
我就用印在我脑子里的这些数字买了号码
and I guess those numbers were stuck in my head, so I played them.
然后我就赢了1亿1千4百万
And I won... $114 million.
接下来事情发生了
That's when it started happening.
我的爷爷死了
My grandpa died,
我的房子着火了
my house caught on fire,
我工作的鸡肉店被流星给撞了...
the chicken joint that I worked at got hit by a meteor...
呃...事实上是陨石
Well, actually, a meteorite.
好了  今晚我在那个舱盖上又看到了这些数字
OK, so, tonight, I see the same freaking numbers on that hatch thing.
刻在边上
Just written on the side.
所以我就想要阻止你们  因为那个东西是被诅咒了的  伙计
And that's why I tried to stop it,because that thing is cursed, man.
你曾经被送进精神病医院?
You were in a psych ward?
-我不是疯子  -我没说你是
-I'm not crazy.  -I'm not saying you are.
那么  好了?  就这样了?
So, what, that's it? That's all?
-你想让我说什么?  -你为什么不相信我?
-What do you want me to say?  -How about you believe me?
Hurley  它们只是数字
Hurley, they're numbers.
医生通过谈话来让病人觉得好过的行为叫什么?
What's that thing where doctors make you feel better just by talking to you?
-医生的举止  -恩  就是那个
-Bedside manner.  -Yeah, that.
你做得糟透了  伙计
Yours sucks, dude.
他怎么样了?
What happened to him?
放松点  好么?
Just try to relax, OK?
我撞上的那辆车
The car that I hit.
那个司机年级较大
The other driver was older...
他在抢救室里死了
He died in the ER.
我全身都没有知觉
I can't feel anything.
我知道
I know.
我怎么了?
What's happened to me?
你的脊椎骨脱臼并骨折了
You have a fracture dislocation of your thoracic lumbar spine,
而且多处是粉碎性的
with multiple crushed vertebrae.
你的背脊断了
Your back is broken.
你的脾撕裂了血都流向了腹部  我们得设法控制住
Your spleen is ruptured and bleeding into your abdomen and has to be stopped.
我会进行外科手术
I'm gonna operate
尽最大可能医好你
and repair as much as possible,
但是最乐观的结果也只能是
but even the most optimistic result puts
保持你腰部以下的感觉能力和移动能力...
the likelihood of retaining any feeling
不过基本上是不可能的了
or mobility anywhere below the waist at extremely unlikely...
Shephard医生?
Dr Shephard,
可以和你说两句么?
may I have a word, please?
那么  我哪儿做错了?
So, what'd I do wrong?
你做错事了?
You did something wrong?
你在皱眉
You're frowning.
我的脸总是这种表情
My face is always this way.
爸爸  嘿  好了
Dad, hey, come on,
说来听听
let's hear it.
偶尔你应该给病人一些希望
You might want to try handing out some hope every once in a while?
即使有99%的可能彻底无药可治
Even if there's a 99 per cent probability
家属们还是会倾向于听到这1%的机会
that they're hopelessly screwed,
这样就没什么问题
folks are much more inclined to hear that one per cent chance that things are gonna be OK.
她的脊椎被碾碎了
Her spine is crushed.
而我告诉她一切都会好的
I tell her that everything's gonna be OK,
那是误导的希望  爸爸
that's false hope, Dad.
也许你是对的
Maybe. Maybe.
但那还是希望
But it's still hope.
我知道我看见了什么
I know what I saw!
是他  是Walt
It was him. It was Walt.
Shannon  轻点声  你会使其他人不安的
Shannon Please lower your voice. You upset others.
我听到了耳语声
I heard whispers.
-哪儿?  -到处都是
-Where?  -Everywhere.
-什么耳语?  -我不知道  是他们
-What whispers? Who?  -I don't know! "Them".
你认为是救生筏出了什么问题了么?
Do you think something happened to the raft?
救生筏没事  Walt和你的丈夫在一起
Nothing happened to the roft. Walt was with your husband, Sawyer...
Sayid  我亲眼看见的
Sayid, I know what I saw!
他们回来了
They're back.
Locke找到了  呃...
Locke found a...
离这儿半英里外的一个舱门
...hatch in the ground about a half mile from here.
我们去把它炸开了  这样大家都可以躲在里面了
We left to blow it open so we could hide inside.
大家都可以躲在里面了  以防万一...
So all of us could hide inside in case...
但是现在不用去考虑这个了 因为那没什么用
But it doesn't matter,it's not gonna work,
今晚我们没有办法下去
there's no way for all of us to get in there tonight.
Jack
Arzt博士呢?
where's Dr Arzt?
呃  他没能和我们一起回来
He didn't make it.
你们看见他们了么?
Did you see them?
你们看到"其他人"了么?
Did you see the Others?
Shannon  没有什么其他人  我们已经谈过了
Hey! Shannon! There are no "Others".We've had this conversation.
一切都会好的
Everything's going to be OK.
我们...我们放松点  我们会没事的
Let's just... let's take it easy.We're gonna be all right.
我们今晚就呆在这儿  好么?  我们一起
We're gonna stay here tonight, OK?Together.
我们还有4把枪  并且会在所有的进出口设岗哨的
We've still got four guns.We'll put lookouts at all the entrances.
只要我们大家呆在一块儿我们就会没事的
We're all gonna be safe as long as we stay together.
太阳在3小时内就会升起
The sun comes up in three hours,
我们都将会看到明天的日出的
and we are all gonna be here to see that happen.
我保证
I promise.
John  你在干什么?
John. What are you doing?
我在弄些绳索
I'm getting some cable.
用来干什么?
What for?
我要下去舱门里看看
It's for the hatch. I'm going in.
你真的认为现在这么做很明智么  John?
You think that's the smartest thing to do right now, John?
我也拿不准
I doubt it.
事实上  你是对的
In fact, you're right.
呆在这里最安全
Safest thing is to stay here.
等着日出
Wait for morning.
等着看那些"其他人"  看看他们是否会露面
Wait for these "Others",to see if they ever show up.
等着救生筏上的勇者带来救兵
Wait for the brave folks on the raft to bring help.
但是我已经等不下去了
But me? I'm tired of waiting.
你相信么?
So, do you believe it?
相信什么?
Believe what?
一切都会好的
That everything's gonna be OK.
是的
Yeah.
我相信
I do.
这有点不像你
Kind of unlike you.
居然如此乐观
The whole glass-half-full thing.
是这样么?
There's a glass?
你做了一件好事  说了你说的那些话...
You did a good thing.Saying what you said.
照顾所有的人
Taking care of everybody.
并且给了他们希望
And just giving them something to count on.
如果你当时不在场  Jack...
If you weren't here, Jack...
我会从舱门里掉下去
I'm going to the hatch.
我知道为什么你不能下去  我是说  他们需要你
I understand why you can't go. I mean,they need you here,
我知道  我真的知道
I get it. I do.
但是不管你反不反对  Locke还是会下去
But Locke's going into that thing whether you like it or not.
那么如果他摔下去摔断了脖子...
And if he falls and breaks his neck...
一起活  单独死  对么?
Live together, die alone, right?
是的
Right.
你的未婚妻伤得很重
Your fiancee was seriously injured.
手术可能会持续10到12个小时
It could take as long as ten,maybe twelve hours.
我只有手术时才能知道她伤得有多重
I won't know how extensive the damage is until I get inside.
她正准备去试衣和挑选桌布
She was going for a dress fitting and to look at tablecloths.
婚礼是...什么时候?
When is it? The wedding?
8个月后
It's eight months.
我保证Sarah在那以前会恢复的...
I'm sure Sarah will have recovered by then, if...
"恢复"?  什么意思?
"Recovered?" What does that mean?
现在正在进行物理治疗  但是如果她真的伤得很重...
There will be ongoing physical therapy,but if she works really hard...
我们能  呃...做爱么?
Will we be able to...you know... make love?
你得知道Sara在她下半辈子可能一直需要
You need to know that there is a chance
很好的专业护理
Sarah might very well need professional care for the rest of her life.
就像...她不能独自去浴室?
What, like, she won't be able to go to the bathroom by herself?
过来
Come here.
我要告诉你一个秘密
I want to tell you a little secret.
来吧
Come on.
近一点
Closer.
可以了
It's OK.
我知道我再也不能跳舞了
I know I'm not gonna be dancing anymore.
但我还是能参加我的婚礼
I can still roll around at my wedding.
到时你也来  好么?
You're invited, OK?
我会医好你的
I'm going to fix you.
本来以为现在你已经下去了
Expected to find you halfway down there by now.
我在等你
I was waiting for you.
那么你是想让我先下去?
So you want me to go down first?
是的  你比较轻
Well, you're lighter.
我能放你下去也能轻松得把你拉上来
I can belay you down and bring you back up just as easy.
通道在下面也可能会变窄
Shaft might get narrower down there, too.
你在上面就是因为你想看看我有没有被什么东西吃掉
You left out the part where you just wanna see if I get eaten by something.
是的  恩  那也是一个原因
Yeah, well. That too.
-不会太紧吧?  -刚好
-Not too tight?  -I've got it.
好了
OK.
等等
Wait.
如果我想停下我该怎么说?
What do I say if need to stop?
"停下"
"Stop."
恩  好的
Right. OK.
好的  我去了
Let's go.
啊  Kate  你还好么?
Kate! Are you all right?
还好
Yeah.
我把手电筒掉了
I dropped the light.
我们也许应该...
Maybe we should...
呃  那好吧
Well, OK, then.
停下
Stop!
看见什么了?
What is it?
John
下面好像有什么东西...
I think there's something down...
Kate  你还好吧?
Kate, are you all right?
Kate
你在说笑吧?
You're kidding, right?
你要回去那儿?
You're going back?
是的
Yeah.
你自己说的要我们等到天亮
What about all that stuff you said about waiting until morning
并且看到日出
and watching the sun rise?
我改变主意了
I changed my mind.
Kate
Locke
混蛋
Damn it!
兄弟  你还好吧?
You all right, brother?
我没事  没事
I'm fine. I'm fine.
放松点  把绑带卸下来
Take it easy, keep the weight off.
来  我看看
Here, let me look.
很痛么?
Does this hurt?
恩  你没有扭伤
Well, you haven't sprained it, then.
但我认为今晚你没机会能追上我了
Don't fancy your chances of catching up, though.
我没想着要追上你
I wasn't trying to catch up.
好吧  你不是这么想的
Oh, aye, 'course you weren't.
你是怎么知道我没有扭伤的?
What do you know about sprains?
我以前可以说是一个医生
I was almost a doctor, once.
世界真是很小
Small world.
那么说你也是医生?
You're a doctor, then?
那你有什么理由?
So what's your excuse?
理由?
Excuse?
跑得好像后面有恶魔追着你一样的理由
For running like the Devil's chasing you?
我的理由...我在训练
My excuse: I'm training.
为了什么训练?
Training for what?
为了跑遍全球
For a race around the world.
我知道很令人惊讶
Impressive, I know.
那么你的理由最好也能说得过去  兄弟
So your excuse better be good, brother.
只是为了想些事情
Just trying to work a few things out.
一个女孩  是么?
A girl, right?
一个病人
A patient.
啊  一个女病人
Ah, but, a girl patient.
她叫什么名字?
What's her name?
她叫Sarah
Her name's Sarah.
那么你对她做了什么?
What'd you do to her, then?
做了什么?
Do to her?
你这么自我摧残肯定是做了一些有价值的事
You must have done something worthy of this self-flagellation.
我告诉她...
I told her...
我做了一个承诺但我无法履行
I made a promise I couldn't keep.
我告诉她我会医好她...
I told her I'd fix her
但是不能
and I couldn't.
我失败了
I failed.
再问一下...
Just one thing...
如果你医好了她呢?
What if you did fix her?
我没有
I didn't.
但是如果你做到了呢?
But what if you did?
伙计  你不知道你现在在说什么
You don't know what you're talking about.
我不知道?  我怎么会不知道?
I don't? Why not?
因为在她的情况看来  能医好那真是奇迹了  兄弟
With her situation,that would be a miracle, "brother".
那你就是不相信奇迹了?
And you don't believe in miracles.
是的
Right.
无论如何我再给你个建议吧
Well, then.I'm gonna give you some advice, anyway.
你得把它抬起来
You have to lift it up.
把它抬起来?
Lift it up?
你的脚踝
Your ankle.
得让它保持住一定的高度
You got to keep it elevated.
聊得真愉快
It's been nice chatting...
Jack
Jack  我是Desmond
Jack, I'm Desmond.
那么  兄弟  祝你好运
Well, good luck, brother.
在新生活中再见了  好么?
See you in another life, yeah?
我不会这么做
I wouldn't do that.
Kate在哪儿?
Where's Kate?
你到底做了...
What the hell's...
我还活着么?
Am I alive?
是,是的  你还活着
Yeah. Yeah, you're alive.
你身上有气味
You smell.
谢谢
Well, thank you.
你身上气味很浓
Wow. You really smell.
是  我...我去跑过步了
Yeah, I went for a run.
好像你跑了很远
You smell like you ran far.
我淋过浴了  我是说  我想我现在不是太酷
Well, I showered.I guess I just didn't cool...
我在一个竞技场里跑步 现在回来想再来看看你
I wanted to get back down here and check on you and...It was a tour de stade.
什么?
What?
就是在体育场的每一个区里上上下下地跑
When you run all the steps in every section of a stadium. Up and down.
你为什么那么做?
Why would you do that?
我很紧张
I'm intense.
那现在好了么?
Did you finish?
没有  我又伤了我的脚踝
No, I hurt my ankle.
真是糟糕
That sucks for you.
Kevin在么?  我的未婚夫
Is Kevin here? My fiance?
我没看见他
I didn't see him.
我肯定他会回来的...
I'm sure he'll be back in a little...
恩  恩  是的  当然
Yeah, yeah. Yeah, absolutely.
能告诉我结果怎么样么?
Are you gonna tell me how it went?
Sarah  你的背部伤得十分厉害
Sarah, the...the damage to your back was extensive.
我尽了我最大的努力  但是你的脊椎骨...我...
I did everything that I could,but your spinal column, I just...
我治不好了
I couldn't repair it.
你的下半身以后永远瘫痪了
You're going to be paralysed from the waist down for the rest of your life.
我很抱歉  我真的很抱歉  Sarah
I'm sorry. I'm so sorry, Sarah.
你在拉我的链条么?
You're yanking my chain, right?
没有
No.
那我怎么能摆动我的脚趾?
Then how come I can wiggle my toes?
你能感觉到么?
Can you feel this?
是的
Yes.
你能感觉到么?
Can you feel this?
是的
Yes.
这儿呢?
This?
是的
Yes.
这儿呢?
This?
是的
Yes.
快滚  不然我杀了他
Move and I'll kill him.
把枪放下
Put the gun down.
Kate在哪儿?
Where's Kate?
Jack  没事的
Jack, it's OK...
-我说了把枪放下  -Kate在哪儿?
-I said, drop it!  -Where's Kate?
-她很好  把枪放下吧  -我不会放手的
-She's fine. Put down...  -I'm not putting down anything!
你想让他死么?
Do you want him to die?
放下枪
Put it down.
这就是你说的么  Locke?
Is this what you were talking about,Locke?
这就是你的命运么?
Is this your "destiny"?
-无论如何都是一个结果  -Jack  冷静一下
-"All roads lead here?"  -Jack, calm down.
放下你的枪  不然我崩了他的脑袋  伙计
Lower your gun, or I'll blow his damned head off, brother!
是你
You?
==============|  YYeTs字幕组招募启示  |==============
英文字幕录制(居住在加拿大和美国)  双语字幕校正   时间轴调整
英语翻译   欧美影视新闻翻译  影视评论  论坛版主  美工人员
服务器提供者  发布宣传  联系地址：www.YYeTs.com
==== YYeTs属于网络爱好者组织 加入者仅凭个人兴趣爱好 无报酬 ====